

Game Producer / Project Manager





acjh13@gmail.com



Highly adaptive and multi-disciplinary Producer / Project Manager. Experienced in leading interdisciplinary teams in fast-paced environments. Keen eye for quality and risk assessment. Passionate about elevating teams to excellence by ensuring smooth processes and pipelines.

Experience

Production Intern | gumi Asia Pte Ltd - *Final Fantasy Brave Exvius* Sept 2020 – Present

- Prepared and maintained monthly and weekly event lists for content updates with <u>Google Sheets</u> and <u>Confluence</u>
- Created and organised tasks for Design team with <u>Jira</u>
- Assisted Associate Producer in integrating new ticketing workflow
- Took initiative to create script to streamline production workflow

Production Teaching Assistant | DigiPen Singapore Sept 2019 – Mar 2020

• Advised student game teams on project scoping and task scheduling

- Mediated cross-discipline discussions and conflicts
- Assisted teams with project scope and scheduling issues

Projects

Producer, Editor Programmer, Cinematics Designer

Kindred | Sept 2019 - June 2020, 35 Weeks | 11 Person Team

- 3D single player narrative game developed on a custom C++ engine and editor with C# scripting
- Worked closely with team members of 4 disciplines
- Communicated game's direction across team members and lecturers
- Adopted Agile methodology with weekly Scrum meetings and Kanban task boards
- Created workflows and pipelines between departments for better communication

Producer, Engine & Editor Programmer

Mega Macho Brothers | Sept 2018 – Apr 2019, 30 Weeks | 7 Person Team

- 2D co-op action platformer developed on a custom C++ engine and editor
- Worked closely with team members of 4 disciplines
- Led and organized weekly meetings with team members
- Worked with lecturers and team members to overcome internal conflicts
- Awarded Unity Best Sophomore Game, DigiPen Game Awards 2019

Education

BSc in Computer Science & Game Design

DigiPen Institute of Technology, Singapore Sept 2017 – May 2021 (Expected)

Dean's Honour List, Fall 2019

Skills

Management Methods

- Agile
- Scrum
- Kanban

Management Software

- Jira
- Confluence
- Trello
- Microsoft Excel / Google Sheets
- HacknPlan

Software & Tools

- Git / SVN
- Slack
- Microsoft Office
- Visual Studio
- Unity
- Unreal Engine 4
- Custom Game Engine(s)

Programming & Scripting

- C / C++
- C#
- Python
- JavaScript